When you're down 'n dirty, it all comes out in The Wash.
The Wash is a action, comedy film directed by DJ Pooh.
With the rent due and his car booted, Sean has to
come up with some ends...and fast.
When his best buddy and roommate Dee Loc, suggests that Sean get
a job busting suds down at the local car wash.
Sean, played by Dr. Dre.
Dee Loc, played by Snoop Dogg.
Slim, played by DJ Pooh.
Antoinette, played by Angell Conwell.
Dewayne, played by Bruce Bruce.
Bear, played by Tommy Lister Jr..
The Wash is a 2001 American comedy film written, produced
and directed by DJ Pooh and starring Dr.
Dre, Snoop Dogg and DJ Pooh, with appearances by Eminem, Ludacris,
Kurupt, Shaquille O'Neal, Xzibit and Pauly Shore.
It was released on November 16, 2001.
The film explores themes of fight, kidnapping, hostage, car wash, illegal drug.
The tone is lighthearted.